We O
have O  
convicted O
terrorists B-person
back O
on O
our O
streets O
and O
we O
have O
ISIS B-company
fighters B-person
back O
in O
our O
country B-geo-loc
its O
the O
religion B-company
of O
peace B-company
Iran B-geo-loc
Crackdown B-company
on O
Mass O
Protests B-person
Leaves O